Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 1, Section 6: Boxes 111-121
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 1, Section 6: Boxes 111-121
- Box: 117, Folder: 16 (Box 117, Folder 16)
  - Item 2: Labor-Management Panel Vol. 1, No. 6, Publication (Box 117, Folder 16)
    February, 1951. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Labor-Management Panel Vol. 1, No. 7, Publication (Box 117, Folder 16)
    March, 1951. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Labor-Management Panel Vol. 1, No. 8, Publication (Box 117, Folder 16)
    April, 1951. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Labor-Management Panel Vol. 1, No. 9, Publication (Box 117, Folder 16)
    May, 1951. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Labor-Management Panel Vol. 1, No. 10, Publication (Box 117, Folder 16)
    June, 1951. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Labor-Management Panel Vol. 2, No. 1, Publication (Box 117, Folder 16)
    September, 1951. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Labor-Management Panel Vol. 2, No. 2, Publication (Box 117, Folder 16)
    October, 1951. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Labor-Management Panel Vol. 2, No. 3, Publication (Box 117, Folder 16)
    November, 1951. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Labor-Management Panel Vol. 2, No. 3, Publication (Box 117, Folder 16)
    December, 1951. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Labor-Management Panel Vol. 2, No. 5, Publication (Box 117, Folder 16)
    February, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Labor-Management Panel Vol. 2, No. 7, Publication (Box 117, Folder 16)
    March, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Labor-Management Panel Vol. 2, No. 8, Publication (Box 117, Folder 16)
    April, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Labor-Management Panel Vol. 2, No. 9, Publication (Box 117, Folder 16)
    May, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Labor-Management Panel Vol. 2, No. 10, Publication (Box 117, Folder 16)
    June, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Labor-Management Panel Vol. 3, No. 1, Publication (Box 117, Folder 16)
    September, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Labor-Management Panel Vol. 3, No. 2, Publication (Box 117, Folder 16)
    October, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: Labor-Management Panel Vol. 3, No. 3, Publication (Box 117, Folder 16)
    November, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: Labor-Management Panel Vol. 3, No. 8, Publication (Box 117, Folder 16)
    April, 1953. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: Labor-Management Panel Vol. 3, No. 9, Publication (Box 117, Folder 16)
    May-June, 1953. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: Labor-Management Panel Vol. 4, No. 1, Publication (Box 117, Folder 16)
    September, 1953. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: Labor-Management Panel Vol. 4, No. 2, Publication (Box 117, Folder 16)
    October, 1953. Item is in English.
  - Item 23: Labor-Management Panel Vol. 4, No. 3, Publication (Box 117, Folder 16)
    November, 1953. Item is in English.
  - Item 24: Labor-Management Panel Vol. 4, No. 4, Publication (Box 117, Folder 16)
    December, 1953. Item is in English.
  - Item 25: Labor-Management Panel Vol. 4, No. 5, Publication (Box 117, Folder 16)
    January, 1954. Item is in English.
  - Item 26: Labor-Management Panel Vol. 4, No. 6, Publication (Box 117, Folder 16)
    February, 1954. Item is in English.
  - Item 27: Labor-Management Panel Vol. 4, No. 7, Publication (Box 117, Folder 16)
    March, 1954. Item is in English.
  - Item 28: Labor-Management Panel Vol. 4, No. 8, Publication (Box 117, Folder 16)
    April, 1954. Item is in English.
  - Item 29: Labor-Management Panel Vol. 4, No. 8, Publication (Box 117, Folder 16)
  - Item 30: Labor-Management Panel Vol. 5, No. 2, Publication (Box 117, Folder 16)
    October, 1954. Item is in English.
  - Item 31: Labor-Management Panel Vol. 5, No. 1, Publication (Box 117, Folder 16)
    September, 1954. Item is in English.
  - Item 32: Labor-Management Panel Vol. 5, No. 3, Publication (Box 117, Folder 16)
    November, 1954. Item is in English.
  - Item 33: Labor-Management Panel Vol. 5, No. 4, Publication (Box 117, Folder 16)
    December, 1954. Item is in English.
  - Item 34: Labor-Management Panel Vol. 5, No. 5, Publication (Box 117, Folder 16)
    January, 1955. Item is in English.
  - Item 35: Labor-Management Panel Vol. 5, No. 6 and 7, Publication (Box 117, Folder 16)
    February-March, 1955. Item is in English.
  - Item 36: Labor-Management Panel Vol. 5, No. 8, Publication (Box 117, Folder 16)
    April, 1955. Item is in English.
  - Item 37: Labor-Management Panel Vol. 6, No. 2, Publication (Box 117, Folder 16)
    October, 1955. Item is in English.
  - Item 38: Labor-Management Panel Vol. 7, No. 1, Publication (Box 117, Folder 16)
    January, 1956. Item is in English.
  - Item 39: Labor-Management Panel Vol. 9, No. 2, Publication (Box 117, Folder 16)
    November-December, 1959. Item is in English.
- Box: 117, Folder: 17 (Box 117, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Administrative Information: Instructions for Placing These Pages in Your Handbook, Publication (Box 117, Folder 17)
    November 1977. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Upjohn Intercom Vol. 17, No. 10, Publication (Box 117, Folder 17)
    October 1979. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Upjohn Intercom Vol. 17, No. 12, Publication (Box 117, Folder 17)
    December 1979. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Upjohn Inter-Comment Vol.7, No. 11, Publication (Box 117, Folder 17)
    June 9, 1978. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: The Equation, Publication (Box 117, Folder 17)
  - Item 6: The Upjohn Company: Job Specification, Publication (Box 117, Folder 17)
- Box: 117, Folder: 18 (Box 117, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Toward Greater Industry and Greater Involvement in Manpower Development: Staff Paper, Publication (Box 117, Folder 18)
    By Samuel M. Burt and Herbert E. Striner. September 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Perspective for Business Expansion: A Memorandum to Kalamazoo Businessmen, Publication (Box 117, Folder 18)
    By Julius T. Wendzel. August, 1949. Item is in English.
- Box: 117, Folder: 19 (Box 117, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Labor Arbitration and the Law in Utah, Publication (Box 117, Folder 19)
    By Sanford H. Kadish. Fall, 1953. Item is in English.
- Box: 117, Folder: 20 (Box 117, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Your Job at Van Realte, Publication (Box 117, Folder 20)
- Box: 117, Folder: 21 (Box 117, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Personnel Division Directive No. 1A, Publication (Box 117, Folder 21)
    December 15, 1943. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Personnel Division Directive No. 2D, Publication (Box 117, Folder 21)
    May 9, 1945. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Personnel Division Directive No. 3, Publication (Box 117, Folder 21)
  - Item 4: Personnel Division Directive No. 4, Publication (Box 117, Folder 21)
  - Item 5: Personnel Division Directive No. 5, Publication (Box 117, Folder 21)
  - Item 6: Personnel Division Directive No. 6, Publication (Box 117, Folder 21)
  - Item 7: Personnel Division Directive No. 7 Amendment-1, Publication (Box 117, Folder 21)
    December 16, 1943. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Personnel Division Directive No. 7, Publication (Box 117, Folder 21)
  - Item 9: Personnel Division Directive No. 8A, Publication (Box 117, Folder 21)
    May 24, 1945. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Personnel Division Directive No. 9A, Publication (Box 117, Folder 21)
    May 1, 1944. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Personnel Division Directive No. 10A, Publication (Box 117, Folder 21)
  - Item 12: Personnel Division Directive No. 11, Publication (Box 117, Folder 21)
  - Item 13: Personnel Division Directive No. 12, Publication (Box 117, Folder 21)
  - Item 14: Personnel Division Directive No. 13, Publication (Box 117, Folder 21)
  - Item 15: Personnel Division Directive No. 14, Publication (Box 117, Folder 21)
  - Item 16: Personnel Division Directive No. 15, Publication (Box 117, Folder 21)
  - Item 17: Personnel Division Directive No. 16, Publication (Box 117, Folder 21)
  - Item 18: Personnel Division Directive No. 17, Publication (Box 117, Folder 21)
  - Item 19: Personnel Division Directive No. 18A, Publication (Box 117, Folder 21)
  - Item 20: Personnel Division Directive No. 19, Publication (Box 117, Folder 21)
  - Item 21: Personnel Division Directive No. 20A, Publication (Box 117, Folder 21)
    December 16, 1944. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: Personnel Division Directive No. 21A, Publication (Box 117, Folder 21)
    March 28, 1945. Item is in English.
  - Item 23: Personnel Division Directive No. 22A, Publication (Box 117, Folder 21)
    July 17, 1944. Item is in English.
  - Item 24: Personnel Division Directive No. 23, Publication (Box 117, Folder 21)
    November 9, 1944. Item is in English.
  - Item 25: Personnel Division Directive No. 24, Publication (Box 117, Folder 21)
  - Item 26: Personnel Division Directive No. 25A, Publication (Box 117, Folder 21)
    March 1, 1945. Item is in English.
  - Item 27: Personnel Division Directive No. 26, Publication (Box 117, Folder 21)
  - Item 28: Personnel Division Directive No. 27A, Publication (Box 117, Folder 21)
    April 10, 1945. Item is in English.
  - Item 29: Personnel Division Directive No. 28, Publication (Box 117, Folder 21)
    February 22, 1945. Item is in English.
  - Item 30: Personnel Division Directive No. 29, Publication (Box 117, Folder 21)
  - Item 31: Personnel Division Directive No. 30, Publication (Box 117, Folder 21)
  - Item 32: Personnel Division Directive No. 31, Publication (Box 117, Folder 21)
  - Item 33: Victor Adding Machine Co. Employment Record, Publication (Box 117, Folder 21)
- Box: 117, Folder: 22 (Box 117, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: The Visking Guaranteed Income Plan, Publication (Box 117, Folder 22)
  - Item 2: The Visking Wage Dividend Plan, Publication (Box 117, Folder 22)
- Box: 117, Folder: 23 (Box 117, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Apprentice Training In Building Trades, Publication (Box 117, Folder 23)
    By D. H. Sawyer, Dwight L. Hoopingarner, Edward F. Kloter, D. Knickerbacker Boyd, G. A. McGarvey, L. H. Dennis, Charles W. Sylvester, John N. Green (Introduction). 1924 Series. Item is in English.
- Box: 118, Folder: 1 (Box 118, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Employment in the Waldorf-Astoria: Fifth Edition, Publication (Box 118, Folder 1)
    December 1943. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Employee Handbook, Publication (Box 118, Folder 1)
- Box: 118, Folder: 2 (Box 118, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: The Charles R. Walgreen Memorial Pension Trust Plan for Employees of Walgreen Co. and its Subsidiaries, Publication (Box 118, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Fountain Employees Instruction Book: Walgreen Drug Stores, Publication (Box 118, Folder 2)
- Box: 118, Folder: 3 (Box 118, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Group Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 118, Folder 3)
- Box: 118, Folder: 4 (Box 118, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Workers Together, Publication (Box 118, Folder 4)
- Box: 118, Folder: 5 (Box 118, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: War Production Drive Communities: Their Establishment and Operation, Publication (Box 118, Folder 5)
    April, 1944. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: War Winning Suggestions in the War Production Drive, Publication (Box 118, Folder 5)
    August 1943. Item is in English.
- Box: 118, Folder: 6 (Box 118, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Tenth Regional Labor Board--Case 10, Publication (Box 118, Folder 6)
- Box: 118, Folder: 7 (Box 118, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Employee Progress Report Plan: A reference manual for those who reportand review employee progress, Publication (Box 118, Folder 7)
    By Washington Gas and Light Co. Revised July 1949. Item is in English.
- Box: 118, Folder: 8 (Box 118, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: "Workers Together:" A Story of Pleasant Conditions in an Exacting Industry Establishment, Waltham Watch Company, Publication (Box 118, Folder 8)
- Box: 118, Folder: 9 (Box 118, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: A Study in Tyranny, Publication (Box 118, Folder 9)
    By Rev. A. Powell Davies, D.D. February 22, 1953. Item is in English.
- Box: 118, Folder: 10 (Box 118, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Union Service Institute, Publication (Box 118, Folder 10)
    July 30-August 4. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Negotiated Health and Welfare Programs in Labor-Management Agreements in the Pacific Northwest, Publication (Box 118, Folder 10)
    By P. W. Cartwright, J. B. Gillingham, W. S. Hopkins. February, 1954. Item is in English.
- Box: 118, Folder: 11 (Box 118, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Pacific Coast Marine Safety Code, Publication (Box 118, Folder 11)
    1949 Revision. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Pacific Coast Longshoremen's Strike of 1934: Statement of Thomas G. Plant, Publication (Box 118, Folder 11)
    By Thomas G. Plant. July 11, 1934. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Overtime on Overtime: Memorandum in Support of H. R. 858 with Amendments to Give the Law Retroactive Effect, Publication (Box 118, Folder 11)
    By Wiiliam Radner, Mary L. Schleifer. March 2, 1949. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Summary of Panel Discussion: Waterfront Employers Association of the Pacific Coast and International Longshoremen's & Warehousemen's Union, Publication (Box 118, Folder 11)
    March 3, 1949. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Waterfront Employers Association of the Pacific Coast: The Steamship Industry, Publication (Box 118, Folder 11)
  - Item 6: The Pacific Coast Longshoremen's Strike of 1934: Statement of Thomas G. Plant, Publication (Box 118, Folder 11)
- Box: 118, Folder: 12 (Box 118, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: "The Role of the Supervisor in Employee Relations"--Conference No. 1, Publication (Box 118, Folder 12)
    Tuesday, 12 September 1950. Item is in English.
- Box: 118, Folder: 13 (Box 118, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Industrial Training Abstracts: Vol. 7, No. 1, Publication (Box 118, Folder 13)
  - Item 2: Industrial Training Abstracts: Vol. 7, No. 2, Publication (Box 118, Folder 13)
  - Item 3: Industrial Training Abstracts: Vol. 7, No. 3, Publication (Box 118, Folder 13)
  - Item 4: The "Toledo Plan" An Analysis, Publication (Box 118, Folder 13)
  - Item 5: The "Toledo Plan" A Digest, Publication (Box 118, Folder 13)
  - Item 6: The "Toledo Plan", Publication (Box 118, Folder 13)
  - Item 7: Wages, Prices and Profits: Third Lecture in Series in Industrial Relations, Publication (Box 118, Folder 13)
    By Dr. Arthur M. Ross. February 14, 1950. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Unionism and Income Distribution: Fourth Lecture in Series on Industrial Relations, Publication (Box 118, Folder 13)
    By Dr. Arthur M. Ross. February 21, 1950. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Strikes in Perspective: Sixth Lecture in Series on Industrial Relations, Publication (Box 118, Folder 13)
    By Dr. Arthur M. Ross. March 7, 1950. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Sociological Approaches to Industrial Relations: Second Lecture in Series on Industrial Relations, Publication (Box 118, Folder 13)
    By Dr. Wilbert E. Moore. February 7, 1950. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Institute of Industrial Relations: The Changing Role of Labor, Management, and Government in the Quest for Security, Publication (Box 118, Folder 13)
    By Edwin E. Witte. Item is in English.
- Box: 118, Folder: 14 (Box 118, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Plan of Organization, Publication (Box 118, Folder 14)
    Effective August 2, 1919; Revised May 1, 1920. Item is in English.
- Box: 118, Folder: 15 (Box 118, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Weirton Steel Program on Understanding the Labor Contract, Publication (Box 118, Folder 15)
  - Item 2: Weirton Steel Program on Understanding the Labor Contract, Publication (Box 118, Folder 15)
  - Item 3: Introduction to Holco, Publication (Box 118, Folder 15)
  - Item 4: Unit #2 Letter to "Gentlemen", Publication (Box 118, Folder 15)
  - Item 5: Unit 3, Publication (Box 118, Folder 15)
  - Item 6: The Plan, Publication (Box 118, Folder 15)
  - Item 7: Insurance, Publication (Box 118, Folder 15)
  - Item 8: Hospitalization, Publication (Box 118, Folder 15)
  - Item 9: Early History of the Annuity Plan, Publication (Box 118, Folder 15)
  - Item 10: Article V--Holiday Allowance, Publication (Box 118, Folder 15)
  - Item 11: Unit #2, Publication (Box 118, Folder 15)
  - Item 12: Session 7 Grievances, Publication (Box 118, Folder 15)
  - Item 13: Instructions, Publication (Box 118, Folder 15)
  - Item 14: Instructions, Publication (Box 118, Folder 15)
  - Item 15: Instructions, Publication (Box 118, Folder 15)
  - Item 16: Job Description Instructions, Publication (Box 118, Folder 15)
  - Item 17: Independent Steelworkers Union, Publication (Box 118, Folder 15)
  - Item 18: Weirton Steel Company: Job Description, Publication (Box 118, Folder 15)
  - Item 19: Job Description Instructions, Publication (Box 118, Folder 15)
  - Item 20: Job Description Instructions, Publication (Box 118, Folder 15)
  - Item 21: Weirton Steel Company: Job Description, Publication (Box 118, Folder 15)
  - Item 22: Weirton Steel Company: Wage Scale, Publication (Box 118, Folder 15)
    June 23, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 23: Instructions, Publication (Box 118, Folder 15)
  - Item 24: Contract, Publication (Box 118, Folder 15)
  - Item 25: Weirton Steel Company: Wage Scale, Publication (Box 118, Folder 15)
  - Item 26: Job Classification, Publication (Box 118, Folder 15)
  - Item 27: Job Classification, Publication (Box 118, Folder 15)
  - Item 28: Contract, Publication (Box 118, Folder 15)
  - Item 29: Schedules: C 1+2 art. 3 sec. C, Publication (Box 118, Folder 15)
  - Item 30: Hospitalization, Publication (Box 118, Folder 15)
  - Item 31: Employees Bulletin Vol. 19 No. 7, Publication (Box 118, Folder 15)
    July 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 32: Employees Bulletin Vol. 25, No. 3, Publication (Box 118, Folder 15)
    April 1958. Item is in English.
  - Item 33: Employees Bulletin Vol. 19, No. 3, Publication (Box 118, Folder 15)
    March 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 34: Employees Bulletin Vol. 20, No. 1, Publication (Box 118, Folder 15)
    January 1953. Item is in English.
  - Item 35: Employees Bulletin Vol. 20, No. 2, Publication (Box 118, Folder 15)
    February 1953. Item is in English.
- Box: 118, Folder: 16 (Box 118, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Steelworking at Weirton, Publication (Box 118, Folder 16)
  - Item 2: West Virginia and its Natural Resources, Publication (Box 118, Folder 16)
  - Item 3: "Good Government and a World at Peace", Publication (Box 118, Folder 16)
    By Ernest T. Weir. June 5, 1951. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Notes on the Foreign Situation Based on a Trip Abroad, Publication (Box 118, Folder 16)
    By Ernest T. Weir. June 19, 1953. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Supplementary Retirement Pay Program: Providing $100 Minimum Monthly Income to Qualified Retired Employees, Publication (Box 118, Folder 16)
  - Item 6: New Joint Contributory Group Insurance Program for Weirton Steel Employees, Publication (Box 118, Folder 16)
    In Effect January 1, 1950. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: WSX Reporter, Publication (Box 118, Folder 16)
    November 1953. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Weirton Steel Company, Publication (Box 118, Folder 16)
    By T. J. Ess. Reprinted from November, 1958. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Weirton--Where Freedom Rings, Publication (Box 118, Folder 16)
    By William A. White. September 22-29, 1951. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Bulletin Eight-Page Special Supplement--New Joint Contributory Group Insurance Program for Weirton Steel Employees, Publication (Box 118, Folder 16)
    Effective January 1, 1950. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Weirton Steel Employees Bulletin Vol. 17, No. 3A, Publication (Box 118, Folder 16)
    March 1950. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Human Relations in Action, Publication (Box 118, Folder 16)
  - Item 13: Holco: A Conference Program on "How Our Labor Contract Operates", Publication (Box 118, Folder 16)
  - Item 14: Holco: A Conference Program on "How Our Labor Contract Operates", Publication (Box 118, Folder 16)
- Box: 118, Folder: 17 (Box 118, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Employee Benefits and Services Program, Publication (Box 118, Folder 17)
  - Item 2: Dialogue, Publication (Box 118, Folder 17)
    January 1976. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: This is Our Story, Publication (Box 118, Folder 17)
  - Item 4: Milestones in the History of Welch Foods Inc., Publication (Box 118, Folder 17)
  - Item 5: Welch Foods Products, Publication (Box 118, Folder 17)
  - Item 6: Origin of the Concord Grape, Publication (Box 118, Folder 17)
  - Item 7: The Grape for the Millions, Publication (Box 118, Folder 17)
  - Item 8: From the Vineyard to the Supermarket, Publication (Box 118, Folder 17)
  - Item 9: Setting the Record Straight, Publication (Box 118, Folder 17)
    November 1975. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: National Grape Co-Op News, Publication (Box 118, Folder 17)
- Box: 118, Folder: 18 (Box 118, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: West Coast Lumber Facts, Publication (Box 118, Folder 18)
- Box: 118, Folder: 19 (Box 118, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: The Coal Operator and the Coal Miner--A Partnership, Publication (Box 118, Folder 19)
    By J. G. Bradley. December 5, 1922. Item is in English.
- Box: 118, Folder: 20 (Box 118, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Mr. Quiz Presents: Highlights of a Pension Plan for hourly paid employees of West Virginia Pulp and Paper Company, Publication (Box 118, Folder 20)
  - Item 2: Mr. Quiz Presents: Highlights of Group Insurance Plan for Employees of West Virginia Pulp and Paper Company, Publication (Box 118, Folder 20)
- Box: 118, Folder: 21 (Box 118, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Emergency Training Program: Westcott Valve Company; East At. Louis, Illinois, Publication (Box 118, Folder 21)
    October 1943. Item is in English.
- Box: 118, Folder: 22 (Box 118, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Announcement: Low Cost Group Insurance Protection for Our Employees, Publication (Box 118, Folder 22)
    July 1940. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Group Insurance for Our Employees, Publication (Box 118, Folder 22)
- Box: 118, Folder: 23 (Box 118, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Western Efficiency Society, Chicago: A Questionnaire Digest on Methods of Wage Payment, Publication (Box 118, Folder 23)
    July, 1918. Item is in English.
- Box: 118, Folder: 24 (Box 118, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Benefit Digest, Publication (Box 118, Folder 24)
  - Item 2: The Engineering Classification Plan Issue 2, Publication (Box 118, Folder 24)
    March, 1961. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Western Electric Engineering Research Center Graduate Study Program, Publication (Box 118, Folder 24)
  - Item 4: Career moves Wstern Electric for Engineering Technology Graduates, Publication (Box 118, Folder 24)
  - Item 5: Western Electric, Publication (Box 118, Folder 24)
  - Item 6: Western Electric Handbook, Publication (Box 118, Folder 24)
  - Item 7: Western Electric: Relations With Employees, Publication (Box 118, Folder 24)
  - Item 8: Technical-Professional Classification Plans at Western Electric, Publication (Box 118, Folder 24)
  - Item 9: Engineering Research Center: Western Electric; Princeton, NJ, Publication (Box 118, Folder 24)
  - Item 10: A Center for Continuing Education, Publication (Box 118, Folder 24)
  - Item 11: Western Electrc: Careers in Engineerng and Science, Publication (Box 118, Folder 24)
  - Item 12: Corporate Education Center: 1976 Management Education Calendar, Publication (Box 118, Folder 24)
  - Item 13: Plan for Employees' Pensions, Disbility Benefits and Death Benefits, Publication (Box 118, Folder 24)
    Effective January 1, 1913; Reprinted May 1, 1944. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Plan for Employees' Pension, Disability Benefits and Death Benefits, Publication (Box 118, Folder 24)
    Effective January 1, 1913; Reprinted December 1, 1949. Item is in English.
- Box: 118, Folder: 25 (Box 118, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Western Electric Company Letter to Veterans of World War II, Publication (Box 118, Folder 25)
    By Western Electric Company, Inc. March 1, 1946. Item is in English.